Oiran! Oiran!
Come on, let's play! Let's play!
Alright then.
Oiran!
Can you read me a story?
Well, certainly.
What should I read?
Let's see, how about...
This one!
Can you read me this story?
When I finish reading hers, alright?
I promise I'll get to yours after.
You can just read mine later.
Read mine later.
Why are you always copying me?
Well, uh...
Now, now, you two.
Oh, that reminds me.
Come see.
I have something to give you two.
What is it?
What are you giving us, Oiran?
Oh, wow!
But why?
These are really special treasures of yours, aren't they, Oiran?
It's alright.
Don't you worry about that.
You're also very special to me.
Which is why I'm giving them to you.
Thank you, Oiran!
Oiran, Oiran!
Put this comb on me!
Hurry, hurry!
Okay, okay.
One at a time.
Oh, though.
Oh, you're really special прим.
There's still a lot of tears of my needs on Mars in the wrong place.
There's still a lot in Lie.
guitar solo
See the next clip...
...
Oh!
true
uh
um
see
ām
yeah
g
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da do da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da!
Nowhere to be found!
That's right!
The one with yellow hair?
Zenko maybe?
She had fainted so we put her to bed to rest.
Now she's not in her room. Should we look for her?
Don't bother. I'm sure that the girl is fine.
It's Ashinuke. What do I care?
She left, so it's not our business. Just forget it.
What? But Master...
Shut the hell up!
Dismissed!
Don't ever mention Zenko's name again.
Tell the others not to either.
This wouldn't have happened if they hadn't got on Oiran Warabihime's nerves.
Both Zenko and Omitsu.
I told you!
There's a demon at my house, alright?
Really?
I'm telling you, it looked like this!
You know what I mean, like this!
Yeah, I totally believe you.
Just hold on a second.
Like this!
Now you see what I'm saying?
Yeah, anyway, Mr. Uzui and Zenitsu should be coming to check in soon.
And it was like this!
I couldn't be any clearer here if I tried!
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Zenitsu won't be coming.
There's no doubt.
This guy's the real deal.
He didn't make a sound.
Not even the slightest puff of air.
Wait, Zenitsu's not coming?
What do you mean by that?
I feel bad now about putting you all through this.
It seems I was so desperate to rescue my wives in time that I made some poor decisions regarding the mission.
As it stands, Zenitsu is missing.
There's been no contact since last night.
You two should leave now.
Now you're ranked too low for this.
If the demon here turns out to be an upper rank, you'll be dead weight.
If you vanish from here, they'll just assume that you're dead.
Therefore, I'm continuing on my own.
Please, Mr. Uzui.
We can help-
Don't be ashamed.
Life is all about survival.
So take this chance and get out.
Get back here, old man!
Maybe he's not able to put his trust in us.
Is it because we're the lowest rank?
We're not the lowest rank now.
We're Kanaway.
We did get promoted.
Huh?
Did you forget the rankings?
We used to be Mizunoto at the very bottom, right?
Well, now we're fourth from the bottom.
Kanaway!
Wait, what?
You guys actually caught up to me?
Eat it, you piss-head!
Crybaby!
We'll be moving past you in no time!
Say that again, you stupid bore!
I'll do you one better!
You ready?
Watch this.
Show me my current ranking.
Cool, huh?
What was that?
What?
They messed with your hand on Wisteria Mountain, right?
I think I remember that, but I'm not sure.
I was so exhausted.
Wisteria Flower Engraving.
You have to say that phrase and flex your muscles to invoke it.
I had no clue we could do stuff like that.
It proves we're Demonslayer Core.
Come on now, cheer up!
That's right!
We don't have time to mope around!
I'll head over to your Okimoto house once night falls.
So wait for me till then.
It's too risky to make a move on your own.
Why should I wait for you?
I still need to finish investigating my own house.
I already told you the Demons had my house, so quit wasting our time!
Wait till night!
How stupid are you?
Do they ever shut up?
That's not what I meant!
Mr. Uzui was patrolling outside of our houses during the night, right?
Ow, ow, ow!
Even so, Zenitsu still disappeared, and the demon over at your place is nowhere to be seen right now!
Minosuke, can you please stop smacking me around?
Which leads me to believe there's a passage that leads into the building!
Passage?
That's right, and it hasn't been spotted going in and out of the house, which means the demon is probably working from the inside.
If that is what's happening here, and it's cleverly disguising itself as a human, then it would kill its victims carefully.
Makes sense, right?
Yeah, it does.
Cleaning up after a murder would be a real hassle.
Washing bloodstains is no easy task.
This is a nightlife district.
Which can be convenient for demons, but also an obstacle.
They've gotta work at night, after all.
It'd be odd if they weren't around.
You're right.
I think Zenitsu and Mr. Uzui's wives are all still alive, so I'll proceed with that in mind.
And I will rescue them.
I want you to take action with that in mind too, Inosuke.
But at the same time, I don't want you to die.
Is that all right with you?
I think everything you said just now is exactly what I was about to say myself.
Oiran, we brought you your tea.
Why, thank you.
I can do the rest of it myself.
You two go on and have dinner.
All right.
We'll be going on ahead then.
Don't be long.
Huh?
I love you, Oiran Koinatsu.
I love you too, Oiran.
How sweet.
I love you both as well.
Now get to dinner, you two.
Okay.
Oiran looked happy, didn't she?
She did.
Those girls are something else.
Miss Koinatsu?
Osumi, it's you.
Forgive me for intruding just now.
However, I have a favor to ask.
I'm leaving the Tokito house after this.
Would you give Master my payment for lodging?
What's going on?
And why are you dressed so...
I had to dress as a woman for my mission.
But I'm actually a guy.
Oh, I already knew that.
Your voice gave it away.
Sorry.
What?
Well, it was obvious from the start.
I've known the whole time.
I admit I was a bit curious
as to what you were up to.
I guess I was busted from the beginning.
But you have your reasons, right?
Were you worried about Suma for real?
Or was that a lie?
No!
I was telling the truth!
I would never lie like that!
As for everyone that vanished,
I promise I'll rescue them.
Why, thank you.
I think I needed to hear that.
Because you see,
I'm actually leaving this district for good tomorrow.
No way, are you really?
You must be ecstatic about that.
It seems there's someone
who would want even me as his wife.
Which makes me so happy.
But that could be why I've been worried sick lately
about those I'm leaving behind.
Even if I thought I knew something was wrong,
I'd have no way of even looking into it.
But that isn't your fault.
Please, don't worry about it.
All you can do is move forward.
And you too.
I don't want you to disappear either, Sumi.
Be careful.
Now then, I'll be off.
I wish you the best.
Thank you, Sumi.
Best of luck to you.
And I'm counting on you
to save Suma.
Right.
Oh, did you forget something?
No, but thank you.
However, I really should devour you
before I do forget.
Since tonight happens to be
your last night here,
you can't leave without saying goodbye.
Not good.
The sun's almost done setting.
I've got to get to Inosuke's place fast.
There's a scent.
It's faint, but it smells sweet.
It's a demon.
It has to be.
And it's nearby.
This is bad.
He's late.
It's almost nightfall
and he's still not here yet.
Way to mess things up,
Soichiro.
I'll just take action by myself.
The spirit of coming through
flowing within my heart.
Come on out, mice!
And bring my swords!
Oh, man.
Uzu is something else, huh?
Muscle.
Muscle!
I gotta thank him
for setting me up
with these muscular mice of his.
I wanna boss around
some ninjoo, too!
Muscle.
Muscle!
It's time
to vanquish a demon!
Big way!
Get down!
Coming through!
What happened to Zenko
and Hinatsuru?
Give me the short version.
And don't even think
about asking questions.
Zenko just disappeared.
Inatsuru fell ill
and so she was sent
to the Kirimise.
Tell me everything
that you think
might be relevant.
Who is it
that you suspect?
You can trust me.
You have my word
that I'll kill
whoever it is.
I'll get revenge
for you.
Omitsu.
It was an Oiran
whose name is
Warabihime.
You'll find her
on the north side.
She lives in the room
that has no light.
Not here.
She must be on the prow
for humans.
I'll head to Hinatsuru
while I try to pinpoint
the demon's presence.
If she's still alive
she might have
some information.
Either way
the demon should be
back here by daybreak.
Then I can dispose of it
with my own two hands.
The scent is strong.
There's no question.
Miss Kuinatsu!
Are you a demon hunter?
Glad you came.
So, how many of you
are there?
I know there's at least
two of you now
that I found that
yellow-haired ugly brat.
Is there a Hashira
with you?
Or is he on his way now?
I can tell
you're not a Hashira.
You seem far too weak.
I have no use
for anyone
who's not one.
Understood?
I'm too late.
But what's going on?
I can't see
Miss Kuinatsu's body.
She's not bleeding.
There's not even
a scent of blood.
In case you're wondering,
I don't devour
dirty people.
Or anyone ugly
for that matter.
There's no doubt.
She's upper six.
Let that poor woman go!
Just who the hell
do you think
you're talking to?
How dare you!
Shh.
She's so fast
I didn't even see her move.
This is an upper rank.
I have no strength
left in my limbs.
And my body's numb.
Calm down.
My body's responding fine.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't even be alive
right now.
The only reason
I can't put strength
behind my attacks
is because I'm afraid.
And I just slammed
into that wall
so obviously
my body is numb.
That demon's weapon
is her belt
that has
supernatural abilities.
She can absorb
humans inside of it.
That's why
no matter how hard
I searched inside
the building,
I couldn't find
a secret path
that a human
could fit through.
All she needs
to abduct humans
is a space
big enough
for that belt.
Are you still alive?
Well,
looks like you're
tougher than I thought.
And those eyes
of yours are lovely,
aren't they?
So lovely
I might just have
to gouge them out
and gobble them up.
The box.
It's not broken.
But the next time
she attacks me,
it's sure to be destroyed.
Sorry, Nezuko.
The shoulder strap broke.
I can't carry you
while I fight.
Don't leave that box.
Unless you feel
that your life
is in danger.
Water breathing!
Fourth form!
Striking tide!
Turbulent!
Turn out!
Oh, my God.
Color me impressed?
Your aerial combat isn't half bad.
And you carefully cut away Koinatsu from my belt.
Very fine sword work indeed.
Ugly as you are.
That was very cute of you.
I think I'm starting to grow fond of you.
Wanna know why?
Cause you're like a rat on the brink of death.
Upper...
Six.
Can I do it?
Without Mr. Uzui, Zenitsu, or Inosuke here?
Can I really do this alone?
No.
It's not a matter of if I can do it.
I have to!
No.
No!
They'll come back in early início service to the sky.
I am hearing people go away and look back at my eyesight
if I hadn't습니까, to uzak.
as we go on,
like it's crazy,
the spirit is dribles for a sudden images.
Dort,
succumbulling,
I'll have a new spring,
the time to bring up,
Oh yeah
Keep me over your neighbor
Yeah
My very own muscle mice
They go into tight spaces where we can't fit
Muscle
And help vanquish demons behind the scenes
Muscle, muscle
You could say they're the Shadow Demon Slayer Corps
And now time for a Taisho-era secret
We took care to assemble only the most passionate mice to train as muscle mice
But they must also be narcissistic enough to fall in love with their own muscles
In other words, they have to have a flair for flashiness
Things are gonna get real flashy
Next in Episode 5
Muscle
These guys are the real deal